Okay.
好的
We've looked at a lot of the distributions you might see in your data
我们已就数据可能出现的分布情况讨论了很多
and used that information to choose a specific summary metric or
并讲解了如何使用那些信息来选择特定的总指标
to understand the sensitivity and robustness of your summary metric.
或理解总指标的敏感性和稳健性
But now, it's time to add a level of rigor.
现在我们需要更加严谨
In order to calculate a confidence interval for your metric,
要为指标计算置信区间
you're going to need two things.
你需要两种数据
You'll need to know the variance or equivalently the standard
你需要了解指标的方差 也就是标准偏差
deviation of your metric and you'll also need to know its distribution.
还需要了解其分布情况
In lesson one, we calculated the confidence interval for
在第一课中 我们讨论了一种概率指标的置信区间
a probability metric, which we assumed followed a binomial distribution.
我们假设它呈二项分布
Then we calculated the standard error,
随后我们计算了标准误差
which was our estimate of the standard deviation using the formula
这是我们对标准偏差的估计值 我们使用了以下公式
the square root of p hat times one minus p hat over n.
p? 乘以 1 减 p? 除以 N 的平方根
Then we calculated the width of the confidence interval or the margin of
随后我们计算了置信区间宽度 也就是误差范围
error, as the z score of our confidence level times the standard error.
等于置信度的 z 分数乘以标准误差
So we definitely needed to know the standard error and
我们必须知道标准误差
we also used the fact that this was a binomial distribution in two ways.
我们还在两个方面利用了这是一个二项分布的事实
First, we use the fact that this was a binomial distribution to get
首先 我们根据这是一个二项分布的事实
this formula for the standard error.
得出这个标准误差的计算公式
And second, this formula for the margin of error depends on the assumption that
第二 我们假设这是一个正态分布
this is a normal distribution.
得出这个误差范围计算公式
And remember, the binomial approaches a normal distribution as N gets larger.
注意 N 越大 二项分布就越趋近于正态分布
So to summarize, if your type of metric is a probability metric, you can usually
总结如下 当指标类型为概率指标时
assume a binomial distribution, which approximates a normal for
你实际上可以假设一个二项分布
a large enough sample size and the estimated variance will be the standard
当样本量足够大时 它会趋近于正态分布
deviation squared or p hat times 1 minus p hat over N.
估计方差的计算公式为 p? 乘以 1 减 p? 除以 N
Now let's talk about some other types of metrics you might see.
现在我们来看你可能遇到的其他指标类型
If your metric is a mean, then by the central limit theorem, your
如果指标是一个平均数 根据中心极限定理
metric will follow a normal distribution if the sample size is large enough.
当样本量足够大时 指标将呈正态分布
And the variants of the metric will be given by the variance of the sample,
指标方差的计算公式为
which I'm representing as sigma hat squared divided by the size of
样本方差
the sample.
sigma hat 的平方除以样本量 N
Notice the distinction between the variance of the sample,
注意样本方差与实际指标方差的区别
that is take each of your data points and then collect the variance of them
样本方差是所有数据点的方差
versus the variance of the actual metric, which means that
而实际指标方差是
if you were to collect a new sample, how would you expect this metric to vary?
在采集新样本时 你希望该指标如何变化
We'll be going over an example of this in a minute.
我们稍后将举例说明这个问题
Now this estimated variance is an analytic result.
这个估计方差是一个分析结果
For other types of summary metrics though,
但是 对于其他类型的总指标
estimating the variance analytically may not be so easy.
从分析角度估计方差可能没有这么简单
Take the median, for example, if the underlying data is normal and
以中位数为例 如果基础数据很标准
the sample is large, then the median will be approximately normal.
且样本量很大 那么中位数将接近正态分布
But if the underlying data is not normal,
如果基础数据不标准
then the median might not be normal either.
那么中位数也可能不呈正态分布
Suppose, for example, you're considering latency and your latency is
例如 假设你在考虑延迟问题 且延迟呈二项分布
a bimodal distribution since some people have a slower internet connection and
因为某些用户的互联网连接速度很慢
some people have a faster type.
而另一些用户的速度很快
Then for a large enough sample, the mean would be normally distributed.
当样本量足够大时 平均数将呈正态分布
Where this blue line is the distribution of the underlined data and
这条蓝色是基础数据的分布情况
the pink line is the distribution of the mean.
粉红线是平均数的分布情况
The median on the other hand, might not be normally distributed.
另一方面 中位数可能不呈正态分布
In this example, you can see it looks pretty crazy.
在这个例子中 你可以看到它很不规律
Other percentiles besides the median might also not be normally distributed.
除中位数以外 其他百分位数也可能不呈正态分布
To estimate the variance of the median,
为了估计中位数的方差
you'd need to make an assumption about how the underlying data was distributed.
你需要假设基础数据的分布情况
And depending on your assumption,
根据你的假设
it might not be easy to estimate the variance analytically.
你或许无法轻松估计其分析方差
So for a median or other percentile, the distribution of the metric depends on
对于中位数或其他百分位数
the distribution of the underlying data and your estimate for
指标的分布情况取决于基础数据的分布
the variance will depend on this assumption as well.
而你对方差的估计也将取决于这一假设
Another type of metric that's often easier to analyze is a count or rather,
另一种通常更易于分析的指标是计数
you're usually looking at the difference between two counts,
准确来说 就是你经常会观察两个计数之间的差异
say the experiment group minus the control group.
例如试验组减去对照组
This difference won't always be normally distributed, but
虽然这种差异并非总是呈正态分布
it often is especially for things like demographic data.
但对于人口这样的数据 则经常呈正态分布
The estimated variance of the difference is the sum of the variances
差异的估计方差即
of the individual variables.
各个变量的方差之和
Other types of metrics, such as rates have more unusual distributions,
比率等其他类型指标的分布情况通常更为不寻常
but they can have analytic solutions.
但是也有分析方法
Rates tend to follow a poisson distribution and
比率通常会呈泊松分布
the variance of the poisson distribution is actually equal to the mean.
泊松分布的方差实际上与平均数相同
So you could estimate it by taking the mean of your sample,
在对其进行估计时 我们可以用平均数作为样本
which I'll call x bar.
也就是 x拔
For your experiment though,
然而在实验中
you would be interested in the difference between two rates.
你可能想关注两个比率之间的差异
That is you would need to estimate the variance of the difference between
也就是说 你想估计两个泊松分布之间的差异
two poisson distributions.
的方差
Or alternatively, you could test that the ratio of the means is close to
或者你可能要测试平均数的比率是否接近一
one and compute the variance of that.
并计算其方差
Unlike for the normally distributed data, these difference in rates aren't
与正态分布数据不同的是 比率中的这些差异
likely to be either poisson or normal in distribution.
可能既不呈泊松分布 也不呈正态分布
You can do this analytically and there are several options.
你可以使用多种方法来进行分析
See the Instructor's Notes.
具体请参阅讲师备注
But most people probably don't want to and it can be a big investment and
不过大多数人可能不会想这么做 因为投资太大
hard to generalize.
而且很难归纳
We'll talk in a minute about other options.
我们稍后讨论其他选项
Finally, businesses often want to use general ratios.
最后 各公司通常会希望使用一般比率
For example, you might want to use the ratio of click-through probabilities in
例如 你可能想使用试验组和对照组的点击概率的比率
your experiment and control group instead of the difference.
而不使用其差异
Like for the median, the distribution and estimated variance of a ratio will
就像中位数一样 比率的分布情况和估计方差
depend on the distribution for the numerator and the denominator.
取决于分子和分母的分布情况
Often, you won't know those distributions and for
你通常不知道它们的分布情况
anything more complicated than two normals,
对于比两个正态分布更复杂的情况
you often won't have an analytic result for the variance.
你通常得不出其方差的分析结果
You've already calculated a confidence interval for
你已经使用二项分布计算出
a probability in less than one using the binomial distribution.
一个小于一的概率置信区间
Now, I'd like you to calculate a confidence interval for
现在请计算一个平均数的置信区间
a mean, which will follow a normal distribution.
它呈正态分布
Suppose that audacity wants to measure the mean number of students that visit
假设优达学城想要测量
their home page each week.
每周访问网站主页的学员的平均数
So they record home page visits for seven weeks and get seven measurements,
他们记录了七周的主页访问量并获得了七个测量结果
one for each week.
每周一个
From this they can computer a mean,
他们可以根据这些数据计算出一个平均数
which I'll represent as N bar by summing the data points and dividing by 7.
我使用 N bar 来表示 计算方法是所有数据点之和除以 7
Now what is the confidence interval for this measurement?
这个测量结果的置信区间是什么？
To answer this, you'll need to calculate the standard deviation of the seven
要回答这个问题 你需要计算优达学城采集的七个计数的标准偏差
counts audacity collected, which I'll call sigma.
我称之为 sigma
You can do this any way you want.
你可以用任何方法来计算
One way would be to enter the numbers into a Google spreadsheet or
其中一种方法是 将数据输入 Google 电子数据表
you can copy the spreadsheet linked in the Instructor's Notes.
或者将数据复制到讲师备注中链接的电子数据表中
To compute the standard deviation, you would type equals and
要计算标准偏差 你需要输入等于号
use the standard deviation function.
并使用标准偏差函数
Then you would select the appropriate range, add a close paren and
然后选择适当的范围 添加结束括号
press Enter.
然后按回车键
Most programming languages also have built in functions to compute
大多数编程语言还内置有计算标准偏差的函数
the standard deviation or you could write your own function.
或者你也可以自己编写一个函数
You'll also need to calculate the standard error for the mean,
你还需要计算平均数的标准误差
which is equal to the square root of the variance.
它等于方差的平方根
That is sigma over the square root of seven,
也就是 sigma 除以 7 的平方根
since seven is the number of data points in our sample.
因为 7 是样本的数据点数量
Use this to compute a 95% confidence interval,
这样就可以为优达学城每周用户平均数的测量结果
around audacity's measurement of the mean number of users per week.
计算出 95% 置信区间
Enter the upper and lower bounds of your confidence interval in these boxes and
请将你算出的置信区间的上限和下限写在这两个方框中
round each answer to the nearest integer.
数值四舍五入至最近的整数